etix.com 2016-06-04

# Etix.com | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

**Last Updated: March 1, 2016**

Etix understands that your right to privacy is very important. This privacy policy applies to our Site and the apps where it appears. It describes how we treat personal and private information which we collect. This policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms and, where applicable, our purchase policy. 

Collected Information 

Etix may collect information from and about you, including but not limited to… 

  * Your name, street address, or other contact information
  * Your credit card number, billing zip code, and other payment and billing information
  * Information you post on our website or a third-party social media site
  * Information about events you like, products you buy, or other demographic information
  * Information about the browser you’re using to access our Site, which site you came from or where you went after, location information or your type of mobile device, etc

How We Collect Information 

Etix may collect information… 

  * Directly from you if you register, post on our Site, ask us a question, etc
  * By using browser cookies, web beacons, and other browser tracking tools
  * From third parties if you use an integrated social media feature on our website or app

How We Use Information 

Etix may use the information we collect… 

  * To respond to your questions or requests
  * To improve our products and services
  * To look at site trends and customer interests
  * For security purposes
  * For marketing purposes
    * You may opt-out of having your online behavior tracked for advertising purposes. To learn more, click [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).
  * For transactional communications
  * As otherwise permitted by law

Sharing Information 

Etix may share the information we collect… 

  * With third parties who perform services on our behalf
  * With our business partners
  * If we believe we must in order to comply with the law
  * With a successor to all or part of our business

Security 

At Etix, e-commerce is a way of life. We understand the importance of online security and utilize the latest advances in technology to ensure your transaction is secure. We address security through “defense in depth”, where we employ a collection of complementary and interlocking methods to keep your information secure and protected. Furthermore, Etix maintains compliance with current security standards, including PCI-compliance. While the Internet is never 100% secure, Etix works constantly to stay on the forefront of online security through multiple levels of encryption and regular external vulnerability scans. For your own protection, use caution when using the Internet and remember: never share your Etix account information. 

Etix complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Etix has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Etix’ certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

Questions 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [support@etix.com](mailto:support@etix.com) or 1-800-514-3849. 

© Sat Jun 04 17:32:04 EDT 2016 Etix, Inc. All rights reserved.
